Apisit Purisan

Software Developer

Phone 083-710-2342 Linkedin linkedin.com/in/apisit-purisan-0775b2288

E-mail name.lod@gmail.com

I am a software developer with 1 year and a half of experience both working in-house and outsourcing. mainly focusing on Full-Stack web development using Angular TypeScript with DevExtreme for Font-end and C# .net Core PgSQL for back-end API. I have collaborated effectively with my own team, external teams and also outside the organization. I am sociability, friendliness, fast learner who enjoys acquiring new knowledge and skills, open to embracing new challenges, and I believe that there is chance for further personal growth and development to get working experience and become professional.

Skill

Front-End JavaScript ,TypeScript ,HTML ,CSS ,PHP

Back-End C# ,JavaScript ,GO ,PgSQL ,SQL ,MongoDB

Technology Angular ,ASP.NET ,React , DevExtreme , Syncfusion ,Git , Fixma

Languages English: Normal command of read, written and communication

Thai: Good command of read, written and communication

Self Learning Able to learn, search and understand by myself quickly for improving myself and

developing new skills outside formal education.

Education

Udon Thani Rajabhat University Bachelor Of Science Program In Computer Science

Experience

July 2022 - Present

MULTITA CO., LTD.: Software Developer

Web Application development with Angular TypeScript, CSS, HTML, C# . NET

- Designed and Developed API to make easier to use data.
- Created Database tables as designed by SA and adjust then as appropriate.
- Developed Web Application as designed by SA and adjust then as appropriate.
- Connected APIs to Web Application
- Deploy API and Web Application
- Unit Test Application
- Gived advice to colleagues
- Find and solve problems together within the team and SA team.

February 2023 - Present

Betimes Solutions CO., LTD (Outsource): Front-End

Web Application development with Angular TypeScript,CSS,HTML

- Developed Web Application as designed by SA and adjust then as appropriate.
- Connected APIs to Web Application
- Find and solve problems together within the team and SA team.

November 2021 - February 2022

SCM S Technologies Co., Ltd (Occupational training)

Practice professional experience in computer science and gain knowledge and experience in software development with AngularJs ,SQI ,API , Linux ,ubantu ,red hat.

- Develop Web Applications as assigned.
- Connected APIs to Web Application
- Modified script in linux, ubuntu, redhat according to customer need